I have an exam today and it is raining so heavily outside.
But you will have to appear for the exam.
So I have to go to college somehow.
So let's get ready quickly.  Are you
ready for the exam or not?  But if you are ready to give the exam then you will have to go.
So
today I am going to college with mom in such heavy rain
and mom is going to drop me.
And the college is already taking my exam.
This rain is also testing me
because as soon as I went out with my mother, the
rain also stopped.  So now we have reached
college.  So we quickly run inside
because we are already late due to the first rain.  Due to
hurry, the
exam has gone so haphazardly and messily that I can't even
tell you and these college teachers
treat us as if we are
terrorists.  I am not allowing any cheating at all, friend.
But no problem, I have
enough confidence in myself to pass the exam.
Now let's go out of the college and
after walking for a while, we take an
auto.  We were saved while going to college
because mom had gone to drop us, but
we are not going to be saved while coming back because this rain
knows that we are coming as a motorbike.  That's why the
rain is not stopping.  Then
my sister brings an umbrella for me and the
poor girl goes away drenched herself and look, a
small Ganga is also flowing here.  If it rains for a little longer,
this road will become a big Ganga and
then one will not be able to walk on it.  Well,
somehow we completed all the missions and reached home
and I am very hungry, so we should eat quickly.